ZAGAN 50 KM
BERITH 10 KM
Hey. What is that?
Mr. En is dead.
All the mushrooms created
by Mr. En's magic have rotted away.
Because of that,
the whole world learned of Mr. En's death.
THE BEGINNING
CHAOS SHOCK
Apparently, the mansion was in total chaos
after I lost consciousness.
Shin and Noi noticed something was off
and returned, but it was already too late.
The culprit escaped through an air duct
and took Mr. En's head with him.
Shin followed the blood trail,
but the culprit's tracks ended abruptly
inside the mansion.
In the end,
the culprit has still not been caught.
Ebisu was looking for Kikurage
with snacks in hand.
Oh, yeah.
Kikurage had also disappeared.
And Chota too.
Even that Nikaido.
Ebisu was laughing as always,
but for some reason,
she looked very lonely.
Shin and the others asked me several times
about the headless man and the culprit
who tried to take Mr. En's head.
But no matter how hard I try to recall,
the darkness of that duct
was too terrifying.
I don't want to remember.
It felt like everything fell apart
in an instant somehow.
His death has had various effects
in every region.
CHAOS SPREADS EVERYWHERE
The Magic World,
ruled by En's overwhelming power,
has lost its leader.
It is expected that the chaos will spread...
It's Noi, right? Come in.
Thanks. Shin, do you have a moment?
SCOOP: MR. EN'S MURDER
UNMASKING THE KILLER
Shin, I hated En.
Since I was a kid,
he used my magic for his own convenience
and was an arrogant mushroom dumbass.
So I'm not sad that En died,
but the mansion is getting
out of control without him.
No one's cooking, cleaning, or working.
And fewer people
are looking for the Cross-Eyes.
Everyone got scared and ran away.
People were afraid of Mr. En,
but thanks to him,
this world was somewhat decent.
Shin, it was the Cross-Eyes boss
who killed En, right?
Almost certainly.
The physical discomfort
Fujita felt right before
was the same
as when he fought him six years ago.
Then let's find him, get En's head back,
and bring him back to life.
But Kikurage,
who is essential, is missing.
Kikurage, Chota, and Nikaido's corpses
haven't been found, right?
They might all still be alive.
What are you going to do now, Shin?
Me? I'm just going to do
my job as a cleaner.
I'm going to find him and kill him.
I'm getting excited.
That's right, Shin!
That's our job!
I completely forgot!
I got tired of thinking
about all the little details.
- I'll take a nap here--
- Go to your own room!
Excuse me.
- What?
- Whoa! Am I interrupting?
- No, you've got it wrong!
- Hello.
Oh, Turkey. It's been a while.
Nikaido.
Nikaido!
Big Brother Kawajiri.
Caiman.
Hey, Caiman.
You've got the wrong guy. I'm Aikawa.
I'm a Sorcerer just like you.
Stop it! I gave up magic.
Because of that power, Yakumo and I...
Nikaido, I'm very lucky. Do you know why?
Yakumo!
If I hadn't used magic...
BLACK BOX
Where is this?
Did I come here
because of this square thing?
I don't even know which button does what.
This thing is useless!
What is this place?!
This river...
It's Uncle and Auntie.
Uncle! Auntie!
Who are you calling "Auntie"?
I'm not that old.
Whose kid is this?
I'm Nikaido, Uncle.
I don't know you.
We just happened to be
taking a walk around here.
Uncle and Auntie seem different
from how they usually are.
Could this be the past?
Then, is this my magic?
Big Bro Kawajiri, I went to the past
by using that square box today.
I met Uncle and Auntie
when they were young there.
Magic that manipulates time
is just a legend. It doesn't exist.
Don't lie, Nikaido.
I'm not lying!
Wait.
Where's Yakumo?
Yakumo?
What do you mean by Yakumo?
What?
Why is everyone pretending
they don't know Yakumo?
It's like she never existed.
When I was a baby,
I floated down this river.
Uncle and Auntie happened to be
passing by and picked me up.
If they had looked away for even a second,
I would've probably stayed...
Yakumo!
AN UNNAMED SOUL
LIES HERE
Nikaido!
Big Bro Kawajiri.
This is a town about 200 kilometers
south of En's mansion.
While you were unconscious,
I bought some healing smoke
and healed our wounds.
Thanks, Asu.
My arms and legs are as good as new.
Wait, why did the healing smoke work?
And my body stopped mushrooming.
He was killed?
No way. How could that happen to En?
Could it have been Caiman?
Who knows?
All I know is
people are saying the Cross-Eyes did it.
The Cross-Eyes?
I don't know if it's Caiman or Aikawa,
but if you plan to chase him, I'm in.
Thanks, Asu.
By the way, when you had nightmares,
you kept calling me "Big Bro Kawajiri."
I don't think I ever told you my name.
And you said I saved you a long time ago.
Maybe this has something to do
with your magic?
Do you remember when we first met?
I was just about to enter
the final stage of the Devil exam.
The last few days of the exam are set
to coincide with the Blue Night Festival.
People who wanted to become my partners
were chasing after me.
Since I couldn't use magic
until the exam was over, I was on edge.
That's when I first met you.
You wouldn't leave my side
for some reason.
And that day...
What will you do?
Use magic?
Give up on the Devil exam
and choose a partner?
If I have to make a contract
with you guys...
- What the...
- Hurry! Get out of here!
I won't let you go... Whoa!
Thanks to you saving me,
I was able to become a Devil.
I went to thank you
after I became a Devil,
but you had already started
thinking about living in the Hole.
With my Devil powers, I learned
that your magic was related to time.
You refused to use your magic
because you had lost something precious.
But you're not the same as you were
when you were a child.
Use your magic, Nikaido.
Use your magic to take back what you lost.
No. I can't, Asu.
My magic is really dangerous.
You were turned back into a Sorcerer
because of me.
I was able to become a Devil
thanks to you.
I don't mind
giving up being a Devil for you.
Asu...
I'll use my magic
to take back what I lost.
Thanks to that En guy dying,
security around the mansion's
gotten thin, Johnson.
We still haven't found the room
where they summon Devils, but--
What is it, Jonson?
What?
Good evening, Hayes.
Haru? You turned back into a Sorcerer?
Surprised, aren't you?
It's a huge success.
What do you mean?
I wanted to surprise you, Hayes.
Both of us are the real me.
But it's dangerous.
If I stay out for too long, I'll die.
This is bad.
I feel more at ease
in this form, after all.
Devils are amazing.
Obviously. We're invincible.
I really want to dissect you.
It's been a while
since I've listened to your nonsense.
Then, to celebrate our reunion,
I'll sing you a song.
What?
Tiny, inferior, insignificant creatures
That's what humans are
I eat them when I'm hungry
But they're not tasty
So lame when scared
They live for 90 years at most
Ah, too funny
That's a song about humans.
It's my hobby to sing about
what I feel at the moment.
Anyway, I was looking for you
because I wanted to ask for your help.
Will you come with me?
Now, now, don't be in such a hurry.
It's not too late to see my special trick.
You've changed a little.
This time, we're going to make the doll
using the fastest baking method.
I never thought I'd be making a doll
of Mr. En in this way.
I hope this will help us catch
the person who killed him.
Leave that to us.
Make a good doll, Turkey.
First, cut the special cheese,
vegetables, and salami.
Next,
put them on this dough
that has been fermented to perfection,
lightly flour it,
and roll it into a circle.
Then stretch it out and make it even.
Next, spread tomato sauce on the dough,
put the toppings on,
and sprinkle on powdered cheese.
Finally,
I'll attach the smoke
I imagined Mr. En with to this oil can,
pour it over the dough,
and put it in the oven.
Now we just have to wait for it to bake.
If we follow the doll,
we'll have to fight the Cross-Eyes again.
I hope it bakes quickly.
Did you forget how we got worked over
by them in the Hydra Forest, Noi?
I remember.
They targeted the places
where you cannot produce smoke.
So you do get it.
So based on the location of the pipes,
Mr. Kasukabe had him write down
the places likely to be targeted.
That brat?!
It should be done baking soon.
Let's cut him out of the dough.
Butt!
It's done.
The doll should head to the corpse now.
But Mr. En's body
from the neck down is in the morgue.
Any chance it'll go there?
Don't worry about that.
The doll will react
to the tumor in the head.
He's already moving.
Let's follow him.
Mr. En.
I hope we get to meet the real you again.
It really is a doll.
It looks like En,
but it's full of flaws and unreliable.
Yeah. He doesn't have
the mushrooms he grows or Kikurage.
Looks like he's killing time,
wandering the mansion.
- Oh, everyone's here!
- Fujita!
Mr. En!
No, it's a doll!
Oh goodness.
Shin, the doll's gone!
What?
The doll of Mr. En can use a Broom?
Shin!
Wait for us!
At this rate, we'll lose him!
Why is that Broom
filled with so much smoke?
You keep chasing him.
I'll get ahead of him from the roof.
Got it!
Damn! He's fast!
This should do it. Take this!
You did well, Noi.
Yes! He's slowing down!
Oh goodness.
I was surprised
when I saw the news that En had died.
But was it really the boss who killed En?
Who else would take En's head?
It had to be the boss!
Even if something happens,
we have a lot of healing smoke.
I was worried
when Dokuga killed the Shaitan guys,
but at least we don't have to fear
En being found dead.
Great timing.
To think the boss will now be back...
Dokuga, are you sure
you know where the boss is?
Possibly.
INCOMING CALL...
- Boss?
- What?
I called you over and over again.
Where've you been?
Is that you, Boss? It's me! Ushishimada!
So it really was you who killed En, Boss!
Is the boss there? What's he saying?
Thank goodness! The boss is alive!
CALL ENDED
He hung up.
Was that really the boss just now?
What do you think? Dokuga.
- Dokuga!
- Oh, dear.
Anyway, let's hurry.
Is Mr. En's head
really in this run-down building?
And probably the Cross-Eyes' boss too.
I can finally get back at that bastard.
All right!
Is something wrong, Shin?
Lately, I feel like
someone's been watching me.
What?
No, it's fine. Don't worry about it.
This is it. I think it's that room.
Is that the boss?
This room?
The boss is in here!
There's someone in there. I'm sure of it.
What do we do?
Let's try opening it. Yeah?
No, we should ring the intercom.
Well, well.
Whoa! Look who's here!
We found the bastards!
The Cleaners from the En family!
THE END
What we learned in Episode 8.
It's crazy how many things
En created with his magic.
Haru loves to sing.
Asu is very mindful of Nikaido.
What we'll learn in Episode 9
is still hidden in chaos.
This is Dorohedoro.